teleportmyjob.com 2016-03-15

# TeleportMyJob.com - Where do you want to be?

### OUR PRIVACY PROMISE TO YOU

At certain points while using TeleportMyJob.com, information is collected that helps with the services we provide our users. We value your privacy and provide you with the following statement to inform and assure you on how we look after your information. 

###  Information Collection

##  Registration

In order to use some services on TeleportMyJob.com you must first complete the registration form and create a user name and password. During registration you are required to give us contact information and some demographics (such as gender, age). Please enter the information as honestly and accurately as possible so we can better tailor the site to our users’ needs.

##  Your Friend’s E-mail Address

At various points throughout TeleportMyJob.com, we offer you the opportunity to send a friend an email telling them about a particular service. **We will only use your friend's email address once in order to send this message.** After this, they will not be sent any more emails from us unless they voluntarily register to any of our services.

We are aware some people may abuse our “Email to Friend” system to send emails to a person who is NOT a friend and does not want to get an email from us. If someone using our system sends you something you don't want, we apologise.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. This is a common web technology used by most modern websites and we use cookies in line with commonly accepted practice.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use a session cookie to make it easier for you to navigate our site and it expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by TeleportMyJob.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers or third parties.

### Web Beacons, Clear GIFS, Web Bugs

TeleportMyJob.com and the advertisers on our site employ a common web tool called clear GIFS or web beacons on the website and in emails. These are used in combination with cookies to allow us to better understand our users’ behaviour. They provide us with basic information such as if an email has been opened, what has been viewed on the website, which ads were clicked on, etc. By using the data provided by these beacons, we are able to hone our site and improve our services. Your personal details are in no way linked to the information gathered from web beacons.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

We DO NOT share your personal information with any third parties without your permission. We do share general data that you have provided us such as age, gender, location etc to provide broad statistics to third party advertisers and partners. This information does not identify individual users and is not linked to your personally identifiable information.

When delivering your information to potential recruiters and employers, your profile and CV/Resume is delivered to through the network. You are responsible to ensure that any information on your CV/Resume that you would like to remain confidential, is removed from the document prior to you uploading it on to the TeleportMyJob.com servers. You are also able to make some profile information private, by accessing the settings area in your control panel.

We reserve the right to supply personal information in order to comply with the law and to enforce user agreement terms or protect the rights, safety or property of TeleportMyJob.com and its users or others.

### Choice & Opt Out

When we ask you for your personally identifiable information, we also give you the choice of whether or not you wish to subscribe to any of our newsletters or third party offers. If, afterwards, you no longer wish to receive these, you may opt out by following the instructions contained within these communications or by logging into the website and editing your profile.

You will be informed if your personal details will be shared with a third party that is not TeleportMyJob.com. You can then make the choice at that point whether to share your details with them.

### Communications from TeleportMyJob.com

## Newsletters

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletters, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you with a way to unsubscribe. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section

## Third Party Offers

If you wish to subscribe to our third party offers, we will use your name and email address to send these promotions to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you with a way to unsubscribe. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section.

## Alerts

If you wish to subscribe to our Alerts service, we will use your name and email address to send the ad alerts you have requested. You can switch these alerts on and off at your convenience. To check and change the status of your alerts you need to visit your Control Panel

## Service-Related Announcements

We will occasionally send you service related announcements when it is necessary, for example, email verification, password resetting or important security and maintenance updates.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to delete your account. You must contact our customer service and ask them to this.

## Customer Service Communication

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcome email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email, or in accordance with your wishes.

### The Security of your Information

The security of your personal information is of highest importance to us. When you enter sensitive information such as a credit card number, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

### Business Transitions

In the event of TeleportMyJob.com going through a business change e.g. a merger, acquisition by another company or a sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will probably be among the assets transferred. Users will be notified by email of any change or control of personal information. 

### Changes to this Statement

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Statement at any time however a notice will be posted on the website or you will be contacted by email if any important modifications are made. 

### Questions? Concerns?

For any questions or suggestions with regards to our Privacy Statement, please e-mail us and we will be happy to respond. Contact Us
